{"bug":[{"level":"1","type":"bug","question":"I have spots and like to fly. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🔴 I have round dots on my body."},{"text":"🍃 I like to land on leaves."},{"text":"⚫ My spots are often black."}],"options":[{"label":"Bee","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ladybug","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Caterpillar","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"2","type":"bug","question":"I make honey. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"💛 I am black and yellow."},{"text":"🐝 I buzz around flowers."},{"text":"🍯 I live in a hive."}],"options":[{"label":"Ant","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bee","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Fly","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"3","type":"bug","question":"I wiggle and crawl before I can fly. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐛 I eat lots of leaves."},{"text":"🦋 I turn into something beautiful.","index":1},{"text":"🏡 I might make a cozy home called a chrysalis."}],"options":[{"label":"Grasshopper","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Butterfly","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Caterpillar","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"4","type":"bug","question":"I march in a line and carry food. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐜 I am very small."},{"text":"💪 I am very strong for my size."},{"text":"🏡 I live in a colony."}],"options":[{"label":"Ant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Spider","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Worm","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"5","type":"bug","question":"I jump very high and eat plants. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌿 I am green."},{"text":"🎵 I make a chirping sound."},{"text":"🦵 I have long legs."}],"options":[{"label":"Bee","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Grasshopper","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Beetle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"6","type":"bug","question":"I fly at night and like light. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌙 I only come out when it's dark."},{"text":"💡 I am attracted to lamps."},{"text":"✨ I am a type of moth."}],"options":[{"label":"Firefly","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Butterfly","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Moth","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"7","type":"bug","question":"I click and glow in the dark. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🔦 I light up at night."},{"text":"💚 My light is usually green."},{"text":"🌃 You can see me in the summer."}],"options":[{"label":"Glowworm","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Firefly","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Beetle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"8","type":"bug","question":"I have long legs and make a web. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🕸️ My home is sticky."},{"text":"🕷️ I have eight legs."},{"text":"🪰 I catch other bugs."}],"options":[{"label":"Ant","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Spider","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Worm","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"9","type":"bug","question":"I can be green or brown, and blend into the leaves of trees. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌳 I look just like a twig."},{"text":"🍃 I am good at hiding."},{"text":"🚶I stay very still, even if you get close"}],"options":[{"label":"Stick bug","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Ladybug","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Caterpillar","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"10","type":"bug","question":"I make a loud noise at night in the summer, and live in trees. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🎶 Only the boys sing."},{"text":"🌳 I shed my skin."},{"text":"🌞 I can spend years underground."}],"options":[{"label":"Locust","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cricket","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cicada","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}}],"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Meow!' and love to chase string. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I like to drink milk."},{"text":"🧶 I purr when you pet me."},{"text":"🐾 I have soft paws."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Woof!' and wag my tail. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I like to chew on bones."},{"text":"🎾 I love to play fetch."},{"text":"🏡 I protect your house."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I quack and swim in the pond. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌾 I eat plants and seeds."},{"text":"🐣 My baby is called a duckling."},{"text":"🧡 My beak is often orange."}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Fish","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I oink and like to roll in the mud. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐷 I have a curly tail."},{"text":"🍓 I like to eat fruits and vegetables."},{"text":"☁️ I am often pink."}],"options":[{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I moo and give you milk. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐄 I live on a farm."},{"text":"🌱 I eat grass."},{"text":"⚫ I often have black and white spots."}],"options":[{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sheep","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I chirp and fly in the sky. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐛 I eat worms and insects."},{"text":"🪶 I have feathers and wings."},{"text":"🐦 I build nests in trees."}],"options":[{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Fish","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I roar and have a big mane. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦁 I am known as the king of the jungle."},{"text":"🥩 I am a carnivore and eat meat."},{"text":"🟡 Male ones are golden in color."}],"options":[{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Wolf","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Fox","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I jump and have a pouch. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🇦🇺 I am native to Australia."},{"text":"🌿 I eat plants and leaves."},{"text":"💪 I have strong legs for hopping."}],"options":[{"label":"Kangaroo","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Deer","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I swim in the ocean and have many teeth. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦈 Some species are apex predators and are feared."},{"text":"🌊 I live primarily in saltwater environments."},{"text":"🐟 I primarily consume other fish and marine animals."}],"options":[{"label":"Shark","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Dolphin","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Whale","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I have a long trunk and big ears. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥜 I enjoy eating peanuts, although it's not my natural diet."},{"text":"🐘 I am the largest land animal on Earth."},{"text":"🌴 My natural habitats are in Africa and Asia."}],"options":[{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Giraffe","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rhino","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}}]}